[
  {
    "gtUsername": "acornell8",
    "name": "Addison Cornell",
    "major": "3rd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "Head TA",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "getMostRecentFiles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#hashtag"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "foodChain"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Anything in the Great Outdoors!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "All the teams"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Any dog under 50 pounds is a cat, and cats are useless\" -Ron Swanson"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Rock-Paper-Scissors"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Firefighter"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "alehman3",
    "name": "Alex Lehman",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "4-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "3-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "sort"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "cornMaze"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "running, speedcubing, eating ice cream"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask)) I guess"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch, not that it's bad, I just never used it in the class"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "hw team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"I believe it was Benjamin Franklin who said, 'You have reached the end of your free trial membership at Benjamin-Franklin-Quotes.com\" -Mr. Peanutbutter "
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Waiting For The End - Linkin Park"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "CS1371 TA"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "do the practice tests"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Why did the chicken cross the road?  To get to the other side."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "arao81",
    "name": "Alex Rao",
    "major": "4th year Electrical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "6-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "6-8"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Software Dev Manager",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "spy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#SciencePorn"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "FieldGoalDenied"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Matlab Coding; Reading"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "Was slapped by a girl because I touched a poster. (it's a long story)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "~"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Testing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "People aren't against you; they're for themselves."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "You want to be an ENGINEER. Quit this doctor crap"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "~"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Cocaine by Eric Clapton"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Wasting time"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "LOL American Pie"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Fireman"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "It's not as hard as everyone else says it is."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Why do programmers mix up Christmas and Halloween? Because Dec 25 = Oct 31"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "aschmitt8",
    "name": "Amanda Schmitt",
    "major": "2nd year CS",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "HW Team STA",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "puzzleBox()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "watching cat videos, playing board games, reading, playing video games, and MATLAB (of course)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "getting locked in my own locker"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "my opinion switches"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "every recitation"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "HOMEWORK TEAM!!!!!!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Nothing happens in contradiction to nature, only in contradiction to what we know of it.\" -- Dana Scully on The X-Files"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "I can't give my past self advice without disrupting the space-time continuum"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "anyone gets anything wrong"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Vena Cava by Lady Lamb"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Macintosh"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "teacher\/actress\/scientist\/author"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "I can't give my past self advice without disrupting the space-time continuum"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "what do you get when you combine a dog and a calculator? A best friend that you can count on!"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "avallamattam3",
    "name": "Ashok Vallamattam",
    "major": "3rd Year Chemical Engineering",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "Course Manager",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "life"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#DontSleepOnDayton"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Election"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Sleeping"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "onesVec = ones(1,length(vec)); sum(onesVec(mask));"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "\"Just a man and his duck\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Team Edward (Foyle)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"If you can't blow them away with your brilliance, baffle them with your bullshit\" -Brandon Smith"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "B = A+A+A+A;"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Ellie Goulding"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Sleeping"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Archaeologist"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "busluel3",
    "name": "Baran Usluel",
    "major": "1st Year Electrical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "6-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Senior Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "getMostRecentFiles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "coding, making, singing, ultimate"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "pro switch obv"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "homework team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC (thinkpad)"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "engineer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "rxiao35",
    "name": "Becca Xiao",
    "major": "2nd Year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "3-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "spy"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "illuminati"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Ultimate frisbee, pottery"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "it's blank."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Pierce- One Ok Rock"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "I am a mac fiend"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Do the homework and practice writing code"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "cs41",
    "name": "Cedric Stallworth",
    "major": "20th year CS Major",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "The one with strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "I like long walks on the strtok, strtokking in the woods, and just really a good strtok whenever I get the chance."
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "One time I was walking down the hall and accidently spilled my strtok all over the floor"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "There is no other function but strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "One time I was teaching and almost forgot to strtok. So embarrassing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "The only team. Jacob. JK strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"To strtok, or not to strtok, that is the question. Wait that isn't a question, always strtok\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Remember to floss your strtok every day."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "there isn't any strtok. So I add it myself."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "\"Sugar pie honey strtok\""
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "I am an olympic strtoker. My strtoks are heard around the world."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Any computer with a strtok."
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "Why was I at bandcamp when I could have been strtoking."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Astronaut. Just kidding, there are no strtoks in space."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Make sure you include a strtok on every line."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Why did the chicken cross the road? To get to the other strtok"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "cokechukwu3",
    "name": "Chima Okechukwu",
    "major": "2nd Year Aerospace Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "4-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "7-8"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "Why"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#matlabisbae"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Celery"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Sleeping"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "Being scolded in front of friends"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Anti"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "Why do tomorrow what you can do today"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Stay in school"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "Someone spells function with a capital F"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Perfect"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Sleeping \u001a"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Mac \u001a is the best"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Famous"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Sleep isn?t due"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "You"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "dvam3",
    "name": "Daniel Alayo-Matos",
    "major": "2nd year Aerospace Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": {
      "day": "monday",
      "time": "3-6"
    },
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "help"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#wethebest"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Clock Hands"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Reading, drawing triangles, listening to other people's conversations"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "Never went to middle school :("
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "If the matlab gods didn't want you to use sum(mask) it wouldn't have denoted logicals as 1 and 0."
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Euch! This tea is nothing more than hot leaf juice!\" -Uncle Iroh"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Get out of your room more."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "Someone uses a for loop instead of masking!!!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "I Feel Good (James Brown)"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Sleeping anywhere on anything in any situation."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "I like em both!"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "I beat up all the band kids."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Astronaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Go to help desk"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Two muffins were in an oven. One muffin says to the other \"it sure is hot in here\". The other muffin responds \"AHHHH a talking muffin\"!"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "dprofili3",
    "name": "Daniel Profili",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "4-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "3-4"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "6-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "strtok()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Anything written by Ethan W"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"I am morally opposed to strtok answers on the TA index\" - Ashok"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "I cry all the time"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "ds182",
    "name": "David Smith",
    "major": "54th Year Aerospace Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "~textscan"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "a what?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "TNT"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "MATLAB modeling"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "neither - length(find(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "switch to what?  FORTRAN?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Never give up ... never give up ... never give up. Winston CHirchill at the Oxford Union."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Grow up. Quickly."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Revelation Song"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "~barf"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "banned camp?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Shouldn't that be 'advice'?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "I sent 10 puns to a friend hoping one would make him laugh, but no pun in ten did."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "dnya3",
    "name": "Debbie Nya",
    "major": "2nd Year Biomedical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "5-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "5-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Binging on movies"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Team length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "HW Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Weston Road Flows - Drake"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Always PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Fashion Designer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Practice"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "mbhuyan7",
    "name": "Dolly Bhuyan",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": {
      "day": "tuesday",
      "time": "3-6"
    },
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "sleeping, eating"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti-switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "test team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Don't quit. Suffer now and live the rest of your life as a champion.\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "(*advice) you do you."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "the opening song in Lion King"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "teacher :)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "(*advice) start homework early, go to recitation, do practice tests"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "a degree from UGA"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "ebates6",
    "name": "Emily Bates",
    "major": "3rd Year Aerospace Engineering",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "6-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "slidinDemDMs"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "reading wikipedia articles"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask) because I'm a heathen"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "I spilled water on myself and then tried to keep teaching as if nothing had happened"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Do your math homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "students forget how to index and try to iterate everything"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "using the wrong words at the wrong times"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "it was delicious and different."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "oceanographer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "What do you call a nosy pepper? Jalape?o business!"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "ewilson72",
    "name": "Ethan Wilson",
    "major": "2nd year Computational Media",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "6-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "Help"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#soccermoms"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Anything written by Daniel P"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Climbing, running, swimming, art, public intoxication, cooking"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "One time I was at a chili?s and had a crush on my waitress, and I tried to hit on her but really I just got scared and ordered the wrong thing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro. It looks cooler"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "My brain committed sudoku once and I had to sit down and remember where I was"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team "
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "?I just want to do hoodrat things with my friends?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Don?t cut hair"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "We run out of pizza"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Old timer - Willie Nelson"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "I am the best overall person"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC "
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Exotic animal breeder (still do kind of)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Don?t cut hair"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "My life is one big joke"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "hwhite35",
    "name": "Hannah White",
    "major": "2nd year Biomedical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "3-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "5-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Senior Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "fifteen"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#shocker"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "play2048"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team!"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "mask == true"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "napping"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "mac"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "a princess!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "What do you call a cow with no legs? Ground Beef!!!"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "jpetrillo3",
    "name": "Juliana Petrillo",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "3-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "3-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "magic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "beeMovie"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Tennis, knitting, cooking"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC!"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Actress"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "jhtay3",
    "name": "Justin Htay",
    "major": "3rd year Electrical Engineering\/Math",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "fft"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "F#"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "harmony"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Piano, Video Games, and chess"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "I was playing piano for a school event and messed up horribly"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Too many to choose from..."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team Teamwork makes the Homework Team Dream Work!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "Anything in Analects"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advice to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Start doing Math competitions now..."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "When a student writes their 900 number instead of their GT Username"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Piano Sonata No. 21 in C Major, Op. 53 (Waldstein) by Beethoven"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Patching the Homework Generator"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "LINUX"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "I dated the drum major"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Baseball player"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advice to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "It's 'extrap', not 'extrapolation'"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "There are two muffins sitting in an oven. One muffin says, 'My, it's hot in here!'. The other muffin says, 'Holy Cow! A Talking Muffin!'"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "krogers34",
    "name": "Kantwon Rogers",
    "major": "7th year Masters in Human Computer Interaction",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "The one with strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "I like long walks on the strtok, strtokking in the woods, and just really a good strtok whenever I get the chance."
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "One time I was walking down the hall and accidently spilled my strtok all over the floor"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "There is no other function but strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "One time I was teaching and almost forgot to strtok. So embarrassing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "The only team. Jacob. JK strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"To strtok, or not to strtok, that is the question. Wait that isn't a question, always strtok\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Remember to floss your strtok every day."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "there isn't any strtok. So I add it myself."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "\"Sugar pie honey strtok\""
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "I am an olympic strtoker. My strtoks are heard around the world."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Any computer with a strtok."
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "Why was I at bandcamp when I could have been strtoking."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Astronaut. Just kidding, there are no strtoks in space."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Make sure you include a strtok on every line."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Why did the chicken cross the road? To get to the other strtok"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "kshah88",
    "name": "Karan Shah",
    "major": "4th year Computer Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Making Star Wars noises"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Mac"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Start homework earlier"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "mnugent8",
    "name": "Maggie Nugent",
    "major": "2nd year Biomedical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "3-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "2-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "strtok()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#stop"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Any of the abc's"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Reading, watching TV, eating"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Team sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Don't really have one yet, but will probably have lots in the future"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Don't worry, you're just as sane as I am.\" - Luna Lovegood"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "People have incorrect function headers"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Carry On Wayward Son"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Sighing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "We evacuated two days in due to a hurricane and I cried tears of joy"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "zoologist"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Go to help desk"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "What did the shy pebble wish? That she could be a little bo(u)lder "
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "mdelgrego3",
    "name": "Megan DelGrego",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "2-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "eml_asteroids"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "beeMovie"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask). work smarter not harder"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "the winning team. (homework team)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "fabulous -sharpay"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "rich person, probably"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "mkumar77",
    "name": "Meha Kumar",
    "major": "2nd year CS",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "7-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "6-8"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Test Team STA",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "Don't know how to use a hashtag, only know how to %comment"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "criminalMinds"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Running, crafts, MATLAB"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "plz I went to MATLAB camp"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Feel free to do a little dance when your code works :)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Q: What did the lake say to the river? A: Water you doing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "oahmed32",
    "name": "Omar Ahmed",
    "major": "2nd year Biomedical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "4-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "6-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "6-7"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "cumtrapz"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#notmypresident"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "March Madness"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "Planned to kiss girl on ferris wheel. Got in ferris wheel line. Girl never showed up. Rode ferris wheel alone."
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"True confidence leaves no room for jealousy'"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "The cheeks won't go away, stop pretending like they will"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Bohemian Rhapsody "
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Mac"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "He who goes to bed with an itchy bottom wakes up with a smelly finger"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "pruiz7",
    "name": "Paula Ruiz",
    "major": "2nd year Mechanical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "7-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "5-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "linspace"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#VeganFromMyHeadTo-Ma-Toes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "pkmnBattle"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Reading, lifting, looking for vegan recipes"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "My friends and I used to make up code names for the people we liked so we could talk about them with no one knowing. One guy I liked was nicknamed \"Socks on a Rooster\". "
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "HW Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Thousands of candles can be lit from a single candle and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases from being shared.\" -Buddha"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Keep rocking the basketball shorts. Their comfortable and real fashion is overrated. "
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "People write incorrect function headers. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Zumba by Don Omar"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Falling up stairs"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "I prefer to appreciate music from a distance. "
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Baby. Everyone thinks you are adorable and takes care of you all the time. Life doesn't get better. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Don't be afraid to scrap what you have so far on a homework problem in favor of a better method of solving it. Keep it simple. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "What do you call a line of rabbits jumping backwards? Receding hair line"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "pkoplik3",
    "name": "Peter Koplik",
    "major": "4th year CS",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": {
      "day": "tuesday",
      "time": "5-8"
    },
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "wrldtrv"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#follow"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "sixDegreesOfWaldo or scottSterling"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Lacrosse, chess"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "I broke a window in one of my classrooms with a bouncy ball. That was one loud teacher."
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask). Definitely."
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti-switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Fortunately, I don't have one. Yet... "
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Tech Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Build a man a fire, and he'll be warm for a day. Set a man on fire, and he'll be warm for the rest of his life.\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Save any video game stuff you have now because it'll be worth a fortune in like 10 years."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "You write 1\/0 instead of true\/false."
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Probably nothing."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Linux, you bottom-feeders."
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "Wait, do you want me to complete the quote?"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "6 year old\/Ninja"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Thank your TAs for all the hard work they do :)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "What did the bird say when he flew into the window? Ohhh the pane..."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "rhurst8",
    "name": "Rachel Hurst",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "5-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "5-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "2-3"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "Makevase"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#poundsign"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "ClockHands"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Running, drinkin coffee, contemplating working out, attempting to think philosophicaly, listening to ted talks"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "All of it"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "I wish I had a good answer for this"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team best team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Don?t worry you?ll end up alright"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "People use loops and it isn?t necessary"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Ain?t no man"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Being me yuh"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "I cried because I was quads and weak"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "A chemical engineer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Start homework earlier"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "rsteppe3",
    "name": "Rachel Steppe",
    "major": "4th year Mechanical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "6-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "4-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "cumsum() because it is hysterical when students try pronounce it to ask you how to properly use it"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "##"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "deAdamize because puns are the worst"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Running, Sleeping, Eating"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch all the way"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "One time a student attempted to ask me on a date (which violates many many rules) so I had to shut him down completely."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "I don't know where I'm going from here, but I promise it won't be boring. ~ David Bowie"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "You're going to regret your gaucho pants"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "Students just draw pictures"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Oh You Pretty Things"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Dissing Adam"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC duh"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "No. I'm not doing this one."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "A supreme court justice."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Just because you cried about the homework the first week doesn't mean you will fail the class."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "Adam trying to be funny."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "sholland36",
    "name": "Seth Holland",
    "major": "1st Year Music Technology",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "5-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "7-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "5-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "image"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#hashtag"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "narutoRun"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "soccer, playing drums, caving, "
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "everything"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Tried to explain how to code the quadratic formula. Forgot the quadratic formula."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team!!"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"I just wanna rap good and not sell breadsticks\" - milo"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "you're probably not gonna become a professional soccer player"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "lol haven't graded a test yet"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Addict With a Pen - twenty one pilots"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "nothing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "MAC. IT MAKES THINGS LOOK PRETTY."
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "never went. phew, dodged that one"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "pro soccer player, duh"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "don't try to do the homework in one day"
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "my life"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "tpatel85",
    "name": "Tej Patel",
    "major": "1st Year Computer Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "7-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "5-6"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "ones()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#NASCAR"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Fixing Cars, Driving Cars, Modifying Cars, Flying Quadcopters"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "All of it. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Lost the MATLAB window in between two screens :("
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Speed has never killed anyone. Suddenly becoming stationary, that's what gets you.\" - Jeremy Clarkson"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "driving."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "truck driver."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Do all the practice tests."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "tali30",
    "name": "Teja Huggins",
    "major": "2nd year Mechanical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "5-6"
      },
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "2-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "fifteen"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#theinternetnamesanimals"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "celery"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Soccer and Ultimate Frisbee"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "My co-TA brought brownies and I told my class to save me a brownie (cause I was busy teaching), then as I said that someone walked up and ate the last brownie... Not really embarrassing but I was sad... and hungry"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team "
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Don't pet the sweaty things and don't sweat the petty things\" - Unknown"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Take more naps. You'll miss them when you're older"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Immigrants - The Hamilton Mixtape"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Soccer player\/Lawyer"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Go to recitation"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "tslattery3",
    "name": "Thomas Slattery",
    "major": "2nd year Mechanical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "5-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "round()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#gt21"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Going to class"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Mechanical Engineer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "tabraham7",
    "name": "Tobin Abraham",
    "major": "3rd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "7-8"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Ping Pong, Singing"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro Switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "Teaching a concept incorrectly, keep rolling with it, and watch it all fall apart on an elaborate example, causing pandimonium amongst the students."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "Not everything on the internet is true -Abraham Lincoln"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Just cause you move a lot doesn't mean you can't have meaningful friends"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "The student didn't even write anything"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Sandy by Dion and the Belmonts"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Being Optimistic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Cow Milker"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Stop playing Smash"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "twolfe8",
    "name": "Triton Wolfe",
    "major": "2nd year Chemical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "2-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "4-5"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "cellfun()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#itsapoundsign"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "Criminal Minds"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Violin, rubix cubes, and reading."
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "I probably repressed it..."
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "Sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "Pro switch"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "My function would not save, damn prism"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "I'm partial to the \" however, I also accept '"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "The answer to number 16 is C"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "Oops, how do I remove the when?"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "Smooth, Carlos Santana"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "Wasting as much time as possible"
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC always"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "I was in orchestra."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "An engineer... huh..."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Stop screwing around with random functions and just do the hw."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "The person reading this."
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "twan8",
    "name": "Tyler Wan",
    "major": "4th year Biomedical Engineering",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "tuesday",
        "time": "2-3"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "3-4"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "3-4"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "cumtrapz()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "kaleidoscope"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "volleyball, ice hockey, movies, baking"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "I once called a girl a whale because I didn't know it was an insult."
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "length(vec(mask))"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "pro"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "I forgot to show up."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Homework Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"Science is whatever we want it to be.\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Bangs are not the way to go."
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "if var == true"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "All We Got"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "creating MATLAB problems about Kanye West"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Spider-Man"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "Learn to use Piazza."
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "any pun"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "vpuligundla3",
    "name": "Virinchi Puligundla",
    "major": "1st Year Aerospace Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "6-7"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "4-5"
      },
      {
        "day": "thursday",
        "time": "2-3"
      }
    ],
    "title": "Developer",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "sum()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#tech"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Doing my homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test Team"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Aerospace Engineer"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "wli343",
    "name": "William Li",
    "major": "4th year Biomedical Engineer",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      {
        "day": "monday",
        "time": "3-4"
      },
      {
        "day": "wednesday",
        "time": "3-4"
      },
      {
        "day": "friday",
        "time": "2-3"
      }
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "why"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#nofilter"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "election"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "basketball"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "never went to middle school"
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "anti"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing recitation story",
        "answer": "pronouncing names while handing back tests"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "homework"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "If you see me in a fight with a bear pray for the bear."
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to your 5th grade self",
        "answer": "Get all the sleep you can. "
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "It's blank. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Song",
        "answer": "The Lazy Song"
      },
      {
        "question": "I am the best in the world at:",
        "answer": "taking naps."
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "PC"
      },
      {
        "question": "This one time at band camp...",
        "answer": "no."
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "astronaut"
      },
      {
        "question": "Advise to yourself while you were taking the class",
        "answer": "There's a MATLAB function for everything. "
      },
      {
        "question": "Best Joke",
        "answer": "The LA Lakers"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "gtUsername": "zschlesinger3",
    "name": "Zach Schlesinger",
    "major": "4th year CS",
    "section": {
      "name": "TBD",
      "location": "TBD",
      "time": "TBD"
    },
    "helpDesk": [
      
    ],
    "title": "",
    "funFacts": [
      {
        "question": "Favorite Matlab Function",
        "answer": "strtok()"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Hashtag",
        "answer": "#strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite Homework Problem",
        "answer": "The one about strtok"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hobbies",
        "answer": "Strtoking"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most embarrassing story from middle school",
        "answer": "The time I forgot to strtok and everyone saw :("
      },
      {
        "question": "Team sum(mask) or team length(vec(mask))",
        "answer": "sum(mask)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Pro switch or anti switch",
        "answer": "I switch sides often."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which team are you on?",
        "answer": "Test team (best team)"
      },
      {
        "question": "Favorite quote",
        "answer": "\"We're not here to make money. We're here to make a difference\" -Ryan Williams (I think)"
      },
      {
        "question": "I cry while grading tests when...",
        "answer": "I see \"Function\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Mac (*barf*) or PC?",
        "answer": "Mac"
      },
      {
        "question": "When I was 5 years old, I wanted to be a...",
        "answer": "Garbage Man"
      }
    ]
  }
]